[
	{
		"Sr.no.": "1",
		"Question": "Anthony De Mello Trophy is associated with Test cricket series played between?",
		"Correct Answer": "Ind and Eng",
		"Option A": "Ind and SL",
		"Option B": "Ind and Aus",
		"Option C": "Ind and Eng",
		"Option D": "Ind and SA",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "2",
		"Question": " 'Playing to Win' is my Biography! Who am I?",
		"Correct Answer": "Saina Nehwal ",
		"Option A": "Saina Nehwal ",
		"Option B": "Mary Kom ",
		"Option C": "Yuvraj Singh ",
		"Option D": "Sachin Tendulkar",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "3",
		"Question": "The first Indian wicketkeeper to score an ODI century?",
		"Correct Answer": "Rahul Dravid",
		"Option A": "Vijay Dahiya",
		"Option B": "Parthiv Patel",
		"Option C": "M.S Dhoni",
		"Option D": "Rahul Dravid",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "4",
		"Question": "How many 400+ scores has India registered in ODIs?",
		"Correct Answer": "5",
		"Option A": "4",
		"Option B": "5",
		"Option C": "6",
		"Option D": "3",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "5",
		"Question": "Who has scored the fastest 300 in test cricket?",
		"Correct Answer": "Virender Sehwag",
		"Option A": "Karun Nair",
		"Option B": "Brendon McCullum",
		"Option C": "Matthew Hayden",
		"Option D": "Virender Sehwag",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "6",
		"Question": "India's highest score in ODIs?",
		"Correct Answer": "418",
		"Option A": "413",
		"Option B": "401",
		"Option C": "418",
		"Option D": "411",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "7",
		"Question": "Youngest Indian to receive the Khel Ratna award?",
		"Correct Answer": "Abhinav Bindra",
		"Option A": "Sachin Tendulkar",
		"Option B": "Virat Kohli",
		"Option C": "Abhinav Bindra",
		"Option D": "Saina Nehwal",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "8",
		"Question": "Which Fashion designer is the daughter of Sir Viv Richards?",
		"Correct Answer": "Masaba Gupta",
		"Option A": "Masaba Gupta",
		"Option B": "Payal Singhal",
		"Option C": "Archana Kochhar",
		"Option D": "Monisha Jaising",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "9",
		"Question": "Mark Waugh is commonly called as?",
		"Correct Answer": "Junior",
		"Option A": "Junior",
		"Option B": "Tugga",
		"Option C": "Julio",
		"Option D": "Pup",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "10",
		"Question": "Who was the 1st ODI captain for India?",
		"Correct Answer": "Ajit Wadekar",
		"Option A": "Bishen Singh Bedi",
		"Option B": "Ajit Wadekar",
		"Option C": "Nawab Pataudi",
		"Option D": "Vinoo Mankad",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "11",
		"Question": "What is Glenn McGrath's nickname?",
		"Correct Answer": "Pigeon",
		"Option A": "Crow",
		"Option B": "Sparrow",
		"Option C": "Penguin",
		"Option D": "Pigeon",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "12",
		"Question": "Being Myself' is the autobiography of which tennis player?",
		"Correct Answer": "Martina Navratilova",
		"Option A": "Venus Williams",
		"Option B": "Amelie Mauresmo",
		"Option C": "Martina Hingis",
		"Option D": "Martina Navratilova",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "13",
		"Question": "Which county did Sachin Tendulkar play for?",
		"Correct Answer": "Yorkshire",
		"Option A": "Nottinghamshire",
		"Option B": "Lancashire",
		"Option C": "Yorkshire",
		"Option D": "Leicestershire",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "14",
		"Question": "Which was the only team to defeat India during the 2007 World T20 Championship?",
		"Correct Answer": "NZ",
		"Option A": "NZ",
		"Option B": "PAK",
		"Option C": "AUS",
		"Option D": "SA",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "15",
		"Question": "Who won the 1992 Cricket WC held in Australia?",
		"Correct Answer": "Pak",
		"Option A": "Pak",
		"Option B": "SL",
		"Option C": "AUS",
		"Option D": "WI",
		"": ""
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "16",
		"Question": "AB De Villiers scored the fastest ODI century in how many balls?",
		"Correct Answer": "31",
		"Option A": "37",
		"Option B": "45",
		"Option C": "60",
		"Option D": "31"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "17",
		"Question": "Who is the captain of Pro Kabaddi League's team U Mumba?",
		"Correct Answer": "Anup Kumar",
		"Option A": "Deepak Mondal",
		"Option B": "Anup Kumar",
		"Option C": "Mohit Chillar",
		"Option D": "Surender Nada"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "18",
		"Question": "The tallest wrestler among the following?",
		"Correct Answer": "Andre The Giant",
		"Option A": "The Big Show",
		"Option B": "The Great Khali",
		"Option C": "Andre The Giant",
		"Option D": "The Undertaker"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "19",
		"Question": "What colour jersey is worn by the winners of each stage of the Tour De France?",
		"Correct Answer": "Yellow",
		"Option A": "Red",
		"Option B": "Black",
		"Option C": "Green",
		"Option D": "Yellow"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "20",
		"Question": "Who won the Cricket Champions Trophy in 2004?",
		"Correct Answer": "WI",
		"Option A": "IND",
		"Option B": "AUS",
		"Option C": "SA",
		"Option D": "WI"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "21",
		"Question": "In football",
		"Correct Answer": " which team is nicknamed 'Galacticos'?",
		"Option A": "Real Madrid",
		"Option B": "Real Madrid",
		"Option C": "Juventus",
		"Option D": "Bayern Munich",
		"": "Chelsea"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "22",
		"Question": "We are One",
		"Correct Answer": " the official song of FIFA world cup 2014 was recorded by?",
		"Option A": "Pitbull",
		"Option B": "Shakira",
		"Option C": "Pitbull",
		"Option D": "Akon",
		"": "Rihanna"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "23",
		"Question": "Which city will host the 2020 Olympics?",
		"Correct Answer": "Tokyo",
		"Option A": "Sydney",
		"Option B": "Toronto",
		"Option C": "Tokyo",
		"Option D": "New Delhi"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "24",
		"Question": "Where is the venue for 2018 Asian games ?",
		"Correct Answer": "Indonesia",
		"Option A": "China",
		"Option B": "South Korea",
		"Option C": "India",
		"Option D": "Indonesia"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "25",
		"Question": "Who was the flag bearer for India in the 2016 Rio Olympics ?",
		"Correct Answer": "Abhinav Bindra",
		"Option A": "Sakshi Malik",
		"Option B": "PV Sidhu",
		"Option C": "Sunil Chhetri",
		"Option D": "Abhinav Bindra"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "26",
		"Question": "Which team won the 2010 World T20 Championship?",
		"Correct Answer": "ENG",
		"Option A": "Ind",
		"Option B": "WI",
		"Option C": "ENG",
		"Option D": "PAK"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "27",
		"Question": "Which team won the 2014 World T20 Championship?",
		"Correct Answer": "SL",
		"Option A": "WI",
		"Option B": "ENG",
		"Option C": "SL",
		"Option D": "AUS"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "28",
		"Question": "Which country will host the 2019 cricket WC?",
		"Correct Answer": "ENG",
		"Option A": "SA",
		"Option B": "IND",
		"Option C": "ENG",
		"Option D": "PAK"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "29",
		"Question": "The term ",
		"Correct Answer": "Cricket",
		"Option A": "Kabaddi",
		"Option B": "Fishing",
		"Option C": "Cricket",
		"Option D": "Tennis"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "30",
		"Question": "Dipa Karmakar",
		"Correct Answer": " a medal winner in Commonwealth Games 2014",
		"Option A": " is associated with?",
		"Option B": "Gymnastics",
		"Option C": "Squash",
		"Option D": "Badminton",
		"": "Gymnastics"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "31",
		"Question": "The only Indian athlete to win 2 individual Olympic medals is?",
		"Correct Answer": "Sushil Kumar",
		"Option A": "Saina Nehwal ",
		"Option B": "Abhinav Bindra",
		"Option C": "Sushil Kumar",
		"Option D": "PV Sindhu"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "32",
		"Question": "Federation Cup",
		"Correct Answer": "Football",
		"Option A": "Hockey",
		"Option B": "Football",
		"Option C": "Cricket",
		"Option D": "Rugby"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "33",
		"Question": "Who among the following was not a Goodwill Ambassador for Rio Olympics?",
		"Correct Answer": "Sania Mirza",
		"Option A": "Sania Mirza",
		"Option B": "Salman Khan",
		"Option C": "AR Rahman",
		"Option D": "Abhinav Bindra"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "34",
		"Question": "What is the national game of India?",
		"Correct Answer": "Hockey",
		"Option A": "Cricket",
		"Option B": "Hockey",
		"Option C": "Kabaddi",
		"Option D": "Badminton"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "35",
		"Question": "India won a bronze at the Rio Olympics 2016 in?",
		"Correct Answer": "Wrestling",
		"Option A": "Wrestling",
		"Option B": "Badminton",
		"Option C": "Shooting",
		"Option D": "Gymnastics"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "36",
		"Question": "The record for highest T20 international chase is held by?",
		"Correct Answer": "WI",
		"Option A": "AUS",
		"Option B": "ENG",
		"Option C": "WI",
		"Option D": "IND"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "37",
		"Question": "Who is called the King of Clay?",
		"Correct Answer": "Rafael Nadal",
		"Option A": "Roger Federer",
		"Option B": "Novak Djokovic",
		"Option C": "Rafael Nadal",
		"Option D": "Juan Martin del Potro"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "38",
		"Question": "Highest team total in T20Is?",
		"Correct Answer": "263",
		"Option A": "263",
		"Option B": "260",
		"Option C": "257",
		"Option D": "245"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "39",
		"Question": "Batsman with most runs in T20 international career?",
		"Correct Answer": "Brendon McCullum",
		"Option A": "Virat Kohli",
		"Option B": "Brendon McCullum",
		"Option C": "Chris Gayle",
		"Option D": "AB de Villiers"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "40",
		"Question": "Who won the Pro Kabaddi League 2016?",
		"Correct Answer": "Patna Pirates",
		"Option A": "U Mumba",
		"Option B": "Patna Pirates",
		"Option C": "Telugu Titans",
		"Option D": "Jaipur Pink Panthers"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "41",
		"Question": "Highest individual score in a T20Is was made by?",
		"Correct Answer": "Aaron Finch",
		"Option A": "Yuvraj Singh",
		"Option B": "AB de Villiers",
		"Option C": "Chris Gayle",
		"Option D": "Aaron Finch"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "42",
		"Question": "Record for fastest 50 in T20Is is held by?",
		"Correct Answer": "Yuvraj Singh",
		"Option A": "Yuvraj Singh",
		"Option B": "AB de Villiers",
		"Option C": "Chris Gayle",
		"Option D": "Aaron Finch"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "43",
		"Question": "Which team has the highest T20 win percentage?",
		"Correct Answer": "AFG",
		"Option A": "Aus",
		"Option B": "AFG",
		"Option C": "WI",
		"Option D": "IND"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "44",
		"Question": "Batsman with most sixes in T20 career?",
		"Correct Answer": "Chris Gayle",
		"Option A": "Yuvraj Singh",
		"Option B": "AB de Villiers",
		"Option C": "Chris Gayle",
		"Option D": "Shahid Afridi"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "45",
		"Question": "Who was the Silver medallist for India in the Rio Olympics?",
		"Correct Answer": "PV Sindhu",
		"Option A": "Dipa Karmakar",
		"Option B": "PV SIDHU",
		"Option C": "Saina Nehwal",
		"Option D": "Sakshi Malik"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "46",
		"Question": "First Indian woman to win an Olympic medal?",
		"Correct Answer": "Karnam Malleswari ",
		"Option A": "Saina Nehwal ",
		"Option B": "MC Mary Kom",
		"Option C": "Karnam Malleswari ",
		"Option D": "Sakshi Malik"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "47",
		"Question": "Who holds the record for highest team score in ODIs?",
		"Correct Answer": "ENG",
		"Option A": "SA",
		"Option B": "ENG",
		"Option C": "AUS",
		"Option D": "IND"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "48",
		"Question": "Who holds the record for the highest successful run-chase in ODIs?",
		"Correct Answer": "SA",
		"Option A": "ENG",
		"Option B": "IND",
		"Option C": "AUS",
		"Option D": "SA"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "49",
		"Question": "Who won the Cricket WC 1987?",
		"Correct Answer": "Aus",
		"Option A": "WI",
		"Option B": "IND",
		"Option C": "AUS",
		"Option D": "PAK"
	},
	{
		"Sr.no.": "50",
		"Question": "Who holds the record for the highest wickets taken in an ODI match?",
		"Correct Answer": "Chaminda Vaas",
		"Option A": "Bret Lee",
		"Option B": "Glen McGrath",
		"Option C": "Shoaib Akhtar",
		"Option D": "Chaminda Vaas"
	}
]